smartphoneware.com 2011-06-06

# Smartphoneware. Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy explains how Smartphoneware may collect, use and aggregate personal information about you on www.smartphoneware.com. 

**Please read this carefully, as your continued use of the website is the evidence that you have consented to the terms below.**

### _Information we collect and how we use it_

####  1\. Personal information 

When you purchase any Smartphoneware product or service we collect personal information like your name, email, your device IMEI, purchase place and date, product informaion, etc. 

This information is necessary for us to fulfil and track status of your order and to provide efficient customer service. 

We do not collect or save any credit card or other payment information. This information is only collected by our payment processing partners like eSellerate, Handango, and others. We do not have access to this information. 

#### 2\. Cookies

Certain features of our website such as the shopping cart, and your mobile device model or platform preferences are using cookies. 

A cookie consists of information sent by a web server to a web browser, and stored by the browser for preference keeping purposes. Cookies and related tools should not harm your computer or mobile device, and they do not identify you personally. 

We use cookies to provide an accurate navigation for our users and automatically present content that match your device selection. 

You may set your browser to notify you when a cookie is sent or to refuse cookies altogether, but certain features of our website will not work without cookies. 

#### 3\. "Automatically Collected" Information

When you access Smartphoneware website, our server may automatically record certain information from your system by using different types of tracking technology. This "automatically collected" information may include Internet Protocol address ("IP Address"), version of software installed, system type, the content and pages that you access on the smartphoneware website, and the dates and times that you visit the website. "Automatically Collected" Information is not linked to personally identifiable information. 

"Automatically Collected" Information is used to understand the usage trends and preferences of our Users, to improve the way the website works and looks, and to create new features and functionality. 

#### 4\. Google Analytics

Smartphoneware uses Google Analytics to analyse the use of this website. Google Analytics generates statistical and other information about website use by means of cookies, which are stored on users' computers. The information generated relating to the website is used to create reports about the use of the website. Google will store this information. Google's privacy policy is available at: http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html. 

### _Sharing Your Personal Data_

Generally, we do not sell, lease, rent or otherwise disclose your personal data to third parties unless we may be obligated by mandatory law to disclose your personal data to certain authorities or other third parties, for example, to law enforcement agencies in the countries where we or third parties acting on our behalf operate. We may also disclose and otherwise process your personal data in accordance with applicable law to defend Smartphoneware's legitimate interests, for example, in civil or criminal legal proceedings. 

### _Collecting the Data of Minors_

Our website is intended for use by adults and is not structured to attract children. We do not directly seek children as users of our products and services without their parents' knowledge and consent. 

Our databases may nevertheless contain personal data of children under 13 due to the fact that it is not always possible to determine precisely the age of the user. If Smartphoneware learns that personally-identifiable information of persons less than 13-years-of-age has been collected we will make reasonable efforts to clear our databases of personal data relating to under age users. 

### _Our Commitment to Data Security_

Smartphoneware uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to Smartphoneware, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission of information, Smartphoneware makes commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of our systems. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards. 

### _Changes to this Privacy Policy_

Smartphoneware may from time to time change this Privacy Policy or change, modify or withdraw access to this site at any time with or without notice. 

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
